[{"answer": "Thank you for having me, by the way.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Why are you here?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "I think you should tell them a little of the backstory about how we first met.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "What do you want to achieve with this interview?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I was late a couple of days when we were just practicing, when it was just rehearsal.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Were you unprofessional?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Doesn't mean I save any.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "$1.8 million a day?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Whatever.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "You know what?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "What is the answer to that?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I heard threats of it, yes, which to me felt like OK, that could be real, it could be just -- you know, just an empty threat, I don't know.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "But did you hear that that was the case?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "HEEN: Absolutely, because then it's now we're into commerce.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "That your behavior then had to be moderated?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "There was one.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Were there repeated warnings as they're trying to suggest to people?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "There was one, but it wasn't -- it wasn't delivered in a way that was -- that was a threat.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "But as you carried on behaving in this manner and it got into the papers, you would be in big trouble?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Well, my hernia didn't heed that warning.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Would it be fair to say you didn't heed that warning?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "You're not going to blame your hernia for all this?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I mean I've been to -- you know, a veteran of these wars -- a veteran of the unspeakable at times.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "And you base that healing plain on previous experience?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Which carries with -- and do you accept it carries responsibility?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Absolutely it does.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "ORGAN: Which are different?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "I think it's a waste of time, because I can't change it.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Do you wish you hadn't gone down certain pathways in the last few months?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "When I said, guys, I don't want to be gone too long, I can't be gone too long, because I'm worried about the crew.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What was that?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, I feel guilty that the perception of it has been that I'm the guy to blame for all of it.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Do you feel guilty about the impact this -- your particular situation has had on the rest of the crew?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "No one is trying to call -- in fact, we're live, right?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Do you believe that there was a subliminal plot at CBS that they wanted to get rid of you?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Possibly.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "You mean like a conspiracy?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Let me ask you a direct question --", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Well, plus it begs the question, why didn't they just replace me after season seven when I was asking for a ton of dough and say, all right, well, no, we're going to do the show, but not with you?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "No, nothing.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Are you under the influence right now of any substance?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "But you took a drug test to prove that you are currently completely drug free.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "It looks pretty cool to me, you know?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "The day before.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Yesterday?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I don't know because not being, you know, held hostage by AA anymore, I don't count my days because it puts such a premium on them and you run around with your days, going, oh god, how was your day, how was your day, boom, I lost my days.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "When was the last time you took a drug?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "You said --", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "And then it's like, where did my days go?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "There's a couple of things I wish I hadn't started.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Do you wish you never got on that step?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Drugs, yes.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What about drugs and narcotics?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Probably more subconsciously, not so much at the forefront of, you know, within the scenario or whatever's taking place.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Where you thought I may die?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "So somebody (INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Little excited, you know?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I just -- I wish people would shift that focus on to themselves and their own family and their own friends and just maybe spend a little more time on their home front.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "That if -- you're on tender hooks with you all the time, that leading your life on the edge like this is a constant worry for family, for friends, for fans, isn't it?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Are you a happy guy?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Well, no, I -- as long as I subscribe to the beliefs of others that build these models that don't really leave any room for individuality or creativity or anything that like, you know, they say you've got to surrender and you've got to get rid of your resentments, sit in a room and like be all lame, you know.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Is it as simple as that?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "HEEN: Well, I mean -- if I was -- I'd first look at the writing.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "How would you have reacted to the star of your number one family comedy, which is watched by families and liked by families, behaving off-screen in the way that you've been behaving?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "And of course the irony is your character's not exactly a saint.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "And it's not -- I don't think it comes close to -- I think it eclipses some of the stuff I'm doing out there on my most epic nights, you know?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Right, but it's OK to smoke cigars, just not cigarettes.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "There's a certain brand alignment here, isn't there?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I think that they in some way think that they have some magic literary influence over me by perhaps writing things and then going, oh, my god, look how powerful we are, now he's doing it.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Do you think there's a hypocrisy there?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Gosh, they -- it's -- I mean, name it.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "And what function do those goddesses perform?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I do, yeah.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "You have two girlfriends, basically?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "The wedge, yes.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "The wedge?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "The wedge is a football term.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "What's the wedge?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Well, now -- with some distance from it, I realize its value and I plan to maintain it and protect it like a precious gem for the rest of my days.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "How far do you feel that sense of responsibility, in terms of your personal behavior?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Well, yeah.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Do you think you got out of control?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say it was as bad.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "It's as bad as you've ever been?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "The one where you had five women coming to your house at 4:00 in the afternoon.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Which bender?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Well, I used to.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "You do take cocaine, right?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Well, I hadn't done any for a while, like seven hours, but I had this hernia thing that was popping out.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "What would you have taken on that particular bender?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "It's a shame.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "When they're on the playground, with their friends, all the embarrassment that comes their way?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "So you never -- you've never had any drugs in the house when your kids were around?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "But that's just common sense and courtesy, right?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Well, it's only illegal if I admit to it.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "If you're running a big network like CBS, are you entitled to say you broke the law, therefore you're in breech of your contract?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "Well, no, of course not.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "But you wouldn't deny taking loads of cocaine?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "No, I'm talking about some of the sources they put -- that's the basket they put all the eggs in.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Isn't that a bit of a moot point?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "I'm on a pink cloud?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "No, I feel more alive.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "Do you feel angry now?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "Yeah, no, I was at my high school weight of like 160.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "You're physically fit?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "Nobody has said that they can't.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Can you get insurance for movies and stuff because of what's been going on?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "He was just, you know, not calling for any advice, just like thought you might like to hear a friendly voice.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "What did Mel say to you?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "Sorry to out you, dude.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Sean Penn?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "He was happy to see me.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "What did he say?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "Do any of them do that to you?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "No, I mean, before -- obviously, now you're off the drugs and stuff.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Oh, you mean during the party or right now?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "Yeah, because they know me.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "And when it's guy like that saying it to you, are they the people you listen to more than anybody on the outside?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "Of course, that's I'm sure one of the elements that might drive it.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "Because you're so competitive, that pressure when you're number one to stay number one, can that in itself drive you to go and seek release, to go and want to go and have a few days getting away from it all?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "Pretty much.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 767, "question": "HEEN: Right, you mean the whole store?", "qSentId": 766}, {"answer": "Only way is up, Charlie.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 771, "question": "Gosh, where do we go from here?", "qSentId": 770}, {"answer": "Those are two incidents where the scoreboard doesn't lie.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Do you regret what happened on those two incidents?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "I have not, no.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Have you ever hit a woman?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "A few people that are very close to you have expressed real concern.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 793, "question": "They're to be hugged and caressed, you know?", "qSentId": 792}, {"answer": "Her initials are B.A. I'll give you that much.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "Who was that?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "Yeah, she was attacking me, though, with a small fork, like a cocktail fork.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 805, "question": "You regret that?", "qSentId": 804}, {"answer": "You can't.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "Is there ever any defense?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "Oh, God, yeah.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 815, "question": "But you regret that incident?", "qSentId": 814}, {"answer": "He loves you.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "Stan, where did you go?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "Get back over here and -- and stop with your silliness.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 847, "question": "What would you say to Stan if he's watching this?", "qSentId": 846}, {"answer": "I have not, no.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "Have you talked to your father?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "No, I'm sure he'll hear something about it in one of these interviews.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "You haven't discussed it with him?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "No, I mean -- he's been out of the country, I think.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 863, "question": "Do you not speak to him much?", "qSentId": 862}, {"answer": "Well, I would love that, yeah.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 870, "question": "Is your game plan to actually end up getting your job back?", "qSentId": 869}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 883, "question": "Do you have it in you to be disciplined enough now to not fall by the wayside?", "qSentId": 882}, {"answer": "No, I was joking about being underpaid.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 889, "question": "Were you joking?", "qSentId": 888}, {"answer": "Funny enough, we have got a clip from Dr. Drew.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 896, "question": "Where's Dr. Drew when you need him?", "qSentId": 895}, {"answer": "Let's take a quick listen to Dr. Drew.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 903, "question": "What are his credentials?", "qSentId": 902}, {"answer": "I think you cannot -- you cannot -- come on, man, that's ridiculous.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 918, "question": "What do you think when you hear that kind of professional?", "qSentId": 917}, {"answer": "Some, yeah.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 926, "question": "Have you seen it work for friends of yours?", "qSentId": 925}, {"answer": "Millions of fans just want the show back on the air.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 957, "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 956}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 959, "question": "What is is the way to make that happen?", "qSentId": 958}, {"answer": "HEEN: I would say, OK, you've agreed to pay the crew four show.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 962, "question": "What would you say if you did?", "qSentId": 961}, {"answer": "I don't -- I guess I would have to play ball on some front.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 969, "question": "What would you then sign up to, in terms of personal behavior?", "qSentId": 968}, {"answer": "You're quite sensitive underneath the brash exterior.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 978, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 977}, {"answer": "I was upset after being kind of picked on and the little bit -- the bad stuff by Chuck and Vanity Cards for eight years.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 982, "question": "Has any of this really upset you, properly upset you?", "qSentId": 981}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 993, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 992}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 999, "question": "Do you regret making the little -- what appeared to be an anti-Semitic dig at him?", "qSentId": 998}, {"answer": "HEEN: Of course I would.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1005, "question": "Would you say sorry to him if you had the chance?", "qSentId": 1004}, {"answer": "That --", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1010, "question": "What's your biggest regret of all this?", "qSentId": 1009}, {"answer": "Again, we have to go back to those moments and bring back a souvenir.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1012, "question": "If you had to do it all over again, what would you do differently?", "qSentId": 1011}, {"answer": "No one from CBS has called in in the last hour.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1019, "question": "You find out that those that can't stand the heat around them -- they don't really have the guts to survive, you know?", "qSentId": 1018}, {"answer": "We gave them the opportunity.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1022, "question": "How much time do we have left?", "qSentId": 1021}, {"answer": "Yeah, I don't have a job.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1029, "question": "You would do that?", "qSentId": 1028}, {"answer": "I have a vision of us getting back on the air for season nine and then doing season ten.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1036, "question": "How do you hope it ends?", "qSentId": 1035}, {"answer": "I have not, because I don't feel like there's any real support there.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1044, "question": "Have you talked to any of them?", "qSentId": 1043}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110228pmt", "aSentId": 1053, "question": "Do they feel you've let them down?", "qSentId": 1052}]